Sorry about that, brothers.
That guy Bro Liu,
insisted you two were suspicious
and took it upon himself to interrogate you.
As you know,
the higher-ups are putting a lot of pressure on us.
I have to give them an answer.
Bro Snake.
It's fine.
I just joined the trade, after all.
It's normal that Bro Liu doesn't trust me.
You...
are just too honest.
Let me tell you,
in our line of work,
the biggest taboo is kindness.
Cut the bullshit.
You messed us up like this,
so you owe us an explanation.
I'll drag Bro Liu over right now
and beat him up, alright?
No need.
I'll get payback on Bro Liu.
You only need to do one thing right now.
Speak.
More money.
Sure.
But with things the way they are,
how can I afford to pay you?
So hurry up and get to work.
Once the company makes money,
you'll be the first ones I pay.
Alright?
Deal.
Bro Snake.
I'll get right on it.
What are you staring at?
Call a doctor!
Right away!
Bro Snake.
You two,
for the next month,
neither of you can leave without permission.
Got it?
As for the performance,
I'm counting on you.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
You scared me to death.
Sir.
Let me explain.
It was really an accident this time.
Do you know how much I lost this time?
Personnel, space, and equipment combined cost millions.
We took strict precautions.
But I really don't know what went wrong.
On your scam list,
a college student died, did you know?
I didn't know.
But what does that matter?
It has alerted the police.
They have a one-month deadline to crack the case.
You better stay sharp from now on.
Yes, understood, Sir.
I'll find you a new place.
Put together a new team for me.
When finding people this time,
you must keep your eyes wide open.
Yes, Sir.
Get lost.
Bro Snake,
what happened?
Look at this mess.
Did you just get chewed out?
Bro Snake,
there's something I don't know if I should say.
Speak.
I just feel that since you're so capable,
there's no need to keep working for others.
All that money,
we could be pocketing it ourselves.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Keep going.
We could totally form a new team
and pull off a big job.
Make enough money all at once.
Don't worry, Bro Snake.
As for the people,
I'll get them for you.
The new team will be set up in no time.
Okay.
I'll leave it to you.
Find some sharp ones this time.
Don't worry.
Bro Snake,
there's one more thing.
About this Li Wen,
he does have the skills,
but he has one major flaw.
What?
Too soft-hearted.
We need to find him a task to toughen him up.
I won't do it again!
Pull me up!
I'll never look again!
I'm sorry! I won't do it again!
Miss, please plead for me!
I'll never look at you again!
Pull me up!
I won't do it again! It's too scary down here!
You like to look, huh?
I'll let you look all you want!
Li Wen.
Bro Snake.
I just took some meds.
I'm a bit groggy.
What the hell?
Feeling guilty?
Nothing like that.
Good.
I've got a new job for you.
A big job so soon?
In this line of work,
getting intel is what you do best.
That dead college girl...
Her mother received a lot of donations.
I heard it's hundreds of thousands.
I'm giving this one to you.
Interested?
You.
Sit next to me and help.
Me?
Yes, you.
Didn't Bro Snake send you to help?
If you screw this up,
watch your ears.
I'll give you a code.
Monitor it for me.
Follow my instructions.
Got it?
Okay.
Drink your medicine, dear.
Dear...
I really can't drink anymore.
I've been a burden to you.
Dear...
Don't you think I'm hurting too?
But for Shanshan's sake,
we both have to live on.
It's the only way to honor
Shanshan's spirit in heaven.
Come on, drink it.
There are still many good people in this world.
Kind people online are already donating to us.
We've already received a portion of it.
Once the money comes in,
you can get the surgery.
Come on, drink up.
Please, drink it.
I have to handle this job myself.
Hello?
Hello.
Is this Huang Shanshan's mother?
Speaking.
Regarding the charity donations for your husband, Mr. Huang Dashan,
the total has reached 400,000.
400,000 is enough.
No need for more donations.
It's enough.
Yes.
The public
cares deeply about your husband's condition,
so the charity funds were raised quickly.
However, the final 80,000
has not cleared yet.
We will need about a month to process it.
Why?
My old man's illness can't wait a month.
The situation is,
because our backend is undergoing an upgrade,
some functions are unavailable.
But we can make an exception
and arrange a special channel for you.
You need to download an APP.
I will send you a link right now.
I've opened it,
but I don't understand it.
You do not need to, ma'am.
It is very simple.
Just follow my instructions.
Oh, okay.
Immediately plant a Trojan in her phone
to prevent police tracking.
Understood.
Captain.
The Informant sent some numbers.
But I don't understand them.
The bold text is a phone number.
Identify the owner immediately.
Yes, sir.
Check this for me.
Officer, I've downloaded it.
Good. Just click confirm.
Found it. It's Huang Shanshan's mother.
Call her immediately to intercept it.
Yes, sir.
I've opened the app.
But I'm a bit clumsy.
I can't figure it out.
Do not worry, Mrs. Huang.
Just enter your bank card number
and your ID number.
Oh, okay.
I can't get through.
Her phone is being controlled.
Da Liu.
Tell the local station to head there immediately.
Xiao Lin.
Xiao Hui.
Follow me.
Yes, sir.
Officer, I've entered them.
I received a number.
That is a six-digit verification code.
Just read it to me.
Oh, okay.
Dear.
Who are you talking to?
Someone from the charity center.
They're checking up on us.
Then make sure to properly
thank them.
Four.
Six.
Sun Ming.
Hurry up.
Seven.
Six.
Is anybody there?
Hello?
Xiao Lin, come with me.
Four.
Two.
Ma'am, open the door!
I'm the police!
Open up, quickly!
Officer.
What are you doing?
Ma'am, you're being scammed.
They're from the charity center.
They're helping us.
No, they aren't.
Officer Sun, right?
Must've felt great raiding my place last time.
I'm here to recover some losses this time.
Not too much to ask, right?
No!
This is our lifesaving money!
Ma'am, open the bank transfer page for me quickly.
Stop wasting time.
It's too late.
I'm so useless.
First, I caused my daughter's death.
And now I'm getting my old man killed too.
We got the money!
We're rich!
Li Wen.
Well done.
Let's sit back and count our cash.